<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog</title><link>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:45:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.hoskin.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 16:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/projects/</guid><description>Most of my projects come from me going &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; that would be really useful thing&amp;rdquo; and then trying to build it.
Civil Service Acronym Buster (Link) The Civil Service as an organisation, runs on Acronyms. Anyone new to a Department or area of work might think that their colleagues are speaking a different language.
This site attempts to document all the acronyms used in order to improve everyone’s understanding in the workplace.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/about-me/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 15:38:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/about-me/</guid><description>Hi there 👋
My name is Sam
I work as a Delivery Manager in the Department for Environment, Food &amp;amp; Rural Affairs. I am career Civil Servant, joing DWP, aged 16, as an apprentice then joining the Fast Steam as an in-service canidate.
This Site This site is buit using Hugo, a Static Site Generater, it uses the Anatole theme. It is deployed thought a GitHub Action and hosted as a static site thought GitHub Pages with a custom domain.</description></item><item><title>Welcome</title><link>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/post/welcome/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.hoskin.xyz/post/welcome/</guid><description>Ahead of me starting my new role, I wanted to set up a place where I could start writing weeknotes or publish/develop any thoguhts that I had in the open.
My goal is to write something weekly (Duh-hoy if I am doing weeknotes) and that is it. So I expect varing decree of post lenght, depth and insight.
The reason I want to do this is that I forgot things very easy.</description></item></channel></rss>