<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:45:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://example.org/projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 16:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/</guid><description>Most of my projects come from me going &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; that would be really useful thing&amp;rdquo; and then trying to build it.
Civil Service Acronym Buster (Link) Civil Service Behaviour Helper (Link) &amp;lsquo;In the Works&amp;rsquo; Projects I have quite a few ideas that are in various degrees of development.
Air Quality Moniter Spaned from the idea of tracking indoor office air quailty and then displaying the data. Learning about large scale data, nodes, apis, Data UI and much more.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>http://example.org/about-me/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 15:38:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/about-me/</guid><description>Hi there 👋
My name is Sam
I work as a Delivery Manager in the Department for Environment, Food &amp;amp; Rural Affairs. I am career Civil Servant, joing DWP, aged 16, as an apprentice then joining the Fast Steam as an in-service canidate.
This Site This site is buit using Hugo, a Static Site Generater, it uses the Anatole theme. It is deployed thought a GitHub Action and hosted as a static site thought GitHub Pages with a custom domain.</description></item><item><title>Welcome</title><link>http://example.org/post/welcome/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/post/welcome/</guid><description>Ahead of me starting my new role, I wanted to set up a place where I could start writing weeknotes or publish/develop any thoguhts that I had in the open.
My goal is complete this weekly (Duh-hoy if you weeknotes) and that is it. So I expect varing decree of post lenght, depth and insight.
The reason I want to do this is that I forgot things very easy. So when it comes reflecting back, my mind often draws a blank.</description></item></channel></rss>